<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>انجليزي on اسطرلاب</title>
    <link>https://asturlab.github.io/tags/%D8%A7%D9%86%D8%AC%D9%84%D9%8A%D8%B2%D9%8A/</link>
    <description>Recent content in انجليزي on اسطرلاب</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>do what ever you want with this</copyright><atom:link href="https://asturlab.github.io/tags/%D8%A7%D9%86%D8%AC%D9%84%D9%8A%D8%B2%D9%8A/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>أسئلة إمتحان الإنجليزي لشهادة إتمام مرحلة التعليم الأساسي لسنة 2014-2015</title>
      <link>https://asturlab.github.io/posts/9th-grade-english-2014-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://asturlab.github.io/posts/9th-grade-english-2014-2015/</guid>
      <description>Doctors are trying to learn more about our genes and how our DNA shapes who we are. True False We use the present simple tense to talk about the future events that are regular or fixed. True False One-third of the world&#39;s tropical rainforests are in Brazil. True False Transpiration is when plants lose water through their leaves. True False The past form of the verb fly is (flown). True False No article is used with general, plural countable nouns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>أسئلة إمتحان الإنجليزي لشهادة إتمام مرحلة التعليم الأساسي لسنة 2015-2016</title>
      <link>https://asturlab.github.io/posts/9th-grade-english2015-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://asturlab.github.io/posts/9th-grade-english2015-2016/</guid>
      <description>There&#39;s a big black hair in my soup. True False Bad cuts need stitches. True False The noun of the verb &#34;cure&#34; is cure. True False The world is divided into 42 time zones with Greenwich. True False Agriculture means farming. True False Steel is used for sharp instruments like scissors. True False He is very healthy. He doesn&#39;t eat fruits and vegetables. True False The Hydropolis Hotle will be the world&#39;s first under water hotel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>أسئلة إمتحان الإنجليزي لشهادة إتمام مرحلة التعليم الأساسي لسنة 2016-2017</title>
      <link>https://asturlab.github.io/posts/9th-grade-english-2016-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://asturlab.github.io/posts/9th-grade-english-2016-2017/</guid>
      <description>The verb &#34;cut&#34; can also be a noun. True False &#34;Boil&#34; means to cook in the oven like bread or pizza True False The word &#34;fare&#34; means how much a journey costs. True False A square has got four sides. True False Navigator is someone who works out direction. True False &#34;Too much&#34; is used with countable nouns. True False The person who does cycling is called a climber. True False A child is (13-19) years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>أسئلة إمتحان الإنجليزي لشهادة إتمام مرحلة التعليم الأساسي لسنة 2017-2018</title>
      <link>https://asturlab.github.io/posts/9th-grade-english-2017-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://asturlab.github.io/posts/9th-grade-english-2017-2018/</guid>
      <description>When the leaves of plants transpire, they lose water. True False Silk comes form animal skins. True False A rectangle has got three sides and three angles True False The largest mosque in the world is in India. True False Steel is used for making cars and sharp instruments. True False The Amazon rainforest is in North America. True False Some object like stones, always float in water. True False When it&#39;s 2:30 in the morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>أسئلة إمتحان الإنجليزي لشهادة إتمام مرحلة التعليم الأساسي لسنة 2018-2019</title>
      <link>https://asturlab.github.io/posts/9th-grade-english-2018-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://asturlab.github.io/posts/9th-grade-english-2018-2019/</guid>
      <description>A &#34;camper&#34; is a person who does climbing
 True False    You can use &#34;might&#34; in conditional type 1 if you are sure about the result
 True False    &#34;Return&#34; means one-way ticket
 True False    We somethimes use &#34;one&#34; as a pronoun instead of repeating the noun
 True False    A pentagon and hexaton are shapes</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
